hi this video explains the importance of
easy onboarding to business Central and
why it's crucial for the growth of your
business Central partner business it's a
clip from a launch event video for 2023
release Wave 2 but it's equally relevant
today let's turn it over to CERN who
will tell us more about
it let's start by Framing the problem
the problem is customers love business
Central so do we and so do you well is
that a problem well kind of is a problem
because there are so many customers who
would like to go to business Central
that they're queuing up outside our door
outside your door in such a way that you
struggle with serving them all and
that's a risk because the risk is one
they will find another partner or even
worse they will find another product so
we need to figure out a way to scale the
channel even more there are simply not
enough human resources to go around
luckily we have tools in the toolbox
that can help us all and you to do just
that before we go there let's start by
looking at the onboarding vision that we
have the vision is simply that any
customer can find explore and start
using business Central plus add-on apps
by
themselves now notice the emphasis on
start using it doesn't mean that all
companies will become 100% proficient
without any
assistance and by themselves doesn't
mean Without Partners but it means that
maybe there's an opportunity to rethink
how you as a partner are involved in the
process what can you do with less
Hands-On and more digital
guidance to help us execute towards that
Vision we see at least four things uh
being necessary one of them is it's
super important that we match and
Prospects and customers are matched with
Partners the right partners and the
right solutions from day one so that
their very first meeting with the
product is as great as it can
be next is our onboarding philosophy is
not to drag all users through all setup
now it is to template as much as
possible and then let users selfs serve
and self- finalize the rest of the
experience that can be an evaluation
experience in a trial but it could also
be in a live setting where they need to
set up the system ready for productive
use and to that end we'd like you to
think about how you can take the
knowledge of your consultants and pack
it into some IP into some apps for app
Source now you have domain knowledge and
you have things that you do over and
over again and that work that you do
over over and over again are great
candidates for being packaged into some
digital guidance asking the customer
questions inside the product leading to
some onboarding scenarios where your
Consultants can then move on and instead
serve I'd say more complex problems more
complex scenarios and help customers
that have those needs instead of
focusing and spending time on all the
basics finally it's super important that
any user can learn while doing inside
the product a user needs to be able to
intuitively understand what's a feature
about why does the page exist what's the
next logical step of course there are
some complex scenarios out there that a
consultant would need to guide the user
but think about how you can support that
kind of a Learning
Journey so to
summarize there's a huge opportunity out
there there are so many customers that
wants to go to BC
that's also a risk so make sure that
you're set up to handle that risk now
scale is critical we simply need to
scale more and you can scale more with
the same resources if you invest in
these onboarding
capabilities and how you do that is
driven by Automation and that's what
this session is all about to learn more
visit
aka.ms BC onboarding thank you for
watching
[Music]